作词 : レン ゾット
作曲 : レン ゾット
In the back seat of your mind
在你脑海角落中
Do you feel as though you’ve always known me?
是不是总觉得与我似曾相识？
Shivers down your spine
背脊不禁一阵战栗
Are you feeling like you’re missing something?
你是不是觉得有些失落？
I could turn your night alive
我能令你的夜晚变得盎然生机
Would it be wrong to trust me?
难道不该相信我吗？
Only inches and inches away
不过是咫尺距离
It’s not black and white
无关是非黑白
There’s only so much words can convey
我只能用这些话来向你表达
I could be human or there could be more that I could say
我成为人类时想说的话就绝对不止这些
So, can you hear?
所以你能听见我的声音吗？
I’m afraid I’ll disappear
我害怕自己会消失
I’m a wanderer, my dear
亲爱的 我浪迹四方
Falling down like lonely tears
犹如孤独的泪 不断滴落
Could you be alone with me?
你能单独陪着我吗？
I’m an untold archetype
我还处于不曾露面过的原始形态
There’s a reason why they all evade me
人们对我避而远之是有原因的
Lost just out of sight?
曾迷失困顿过吗？
Well you won’t be alone now
没关系，你不再会是独自一人
I could be yours
你能拥有我
Kept alive in the shallow breaths you try to hide
我会存在你试图屏住的微弱气息中
Only inches away
不过是咫尺距离
So can you hear?
你能否听到我的声音
I’ve lived here, I’ve lived here waiting
我在这等待你的到来
It’s been some time
自始至终
I can’t take it anymore
但我耐心已经被耗尽
I’m one step behind
与你相差一步之遥
So can you hear?
所以你能否听到我的声音
I’m afraid I’ll disappear
我害怕自己会消失
I’m a wanderer, my dear
亲爱的 我浪迹四方
Falling down like lonely tears
犹如孤独的泪 不断滴落
Could you be alone with me?
你能单独陪着我吗
It’s not black and white
无关是非黑白
there’s only so much words can convey
我只能用这些话来向你表达
I could be human or there could be more that I could say
我成为人类时想说的话就绝对不止这些
So can you hear?
所以你能否听到我的声音
Can you hear?
你能否听到我的声音
I’m afraid I’ll disappear
我害怕自己会消失
I’m a wanderer, my dear
亲爱的 我浪迹四方
Falling down like lonely tears
犹如孤独的泪 不断滴落
Could you be alone with me?
你能单独陪着我吗